[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Venus is classified as Earths sister planet.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What chinchilla species has become extinct as a result of fur hunting?", "correct_answer": "Giant Chinchilla", "incorrect_answers": ["All of these", "Long-tailed Chinchilla", "Red-nosed Chinchilla"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Wat Chiang Man is a temple in Thailand. In it, fifteen of these animals represent a sea of unformed matter upon which the cosmos of the Chedi floats.", "correct_answer": "Elephants", "incorrect_answers": ["Fish", "Monkeys", "Birds"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which movie contains this quote: Why anyone would wanna be an orphan is beyond me.?", "correct_answer": "Annie", "incorrect_answers": ["Cheaper by the Dozen", "Big Daddy", "Oliver Twist"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which dogs die in the movie Eight Below?", "correct_answer": "Dewey and Old Jack", "incorrect_answers": ["Old Jack and Shadow", "None die", "Dewey and Maya"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many songs do 80 gigabyte iPods hold up to?", "correct_answer": "20,000", "incorrect_answers": ["45,000", "28,000", "34,000"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What science deals with fermentation?", "correct_answer": "zymology", "incorrect_answers": ["cytology", "virology", "limnology"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Scorpions are active at night in order to avoid which of their predators?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Mice", "Lizards", "Centipedes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which character from Arsenic and Old Lace says the words: right out here in the open with everyone looking?", "correct_answer": "Elaine", "incorrect_answers": ["Dr. Einstein", "Aunt Abby", "Jonathan"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The famous fictional modern detective Philip Marlowe was played by many actors over the years, from Humphrey Bogart to Elliot Gould.  Can you name the author who created him.", "correct_answer": "Raymond Chandler", "incorrect_answers": ["Dashiell Hammett", "Mickey Spilane", "Cornell Woolrich"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The purpose of the striped fur of most tigers species is camouflage.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "According to the Bible, where was Jesus Christ born?", "correct_answer": "Bethlehem", "incorrect_answers": ["Jerusalem", "Erichon", "Egypt"]}]